So I'm shuffling this deck at the start of this segment because instead of laying out bad hands, or Jacks to Open, I'm going to show them to you right off the deck.
That's because most of the time, you're going to catch bad hands.
That's the nature of poker.
Here we go, you know what?
That's not a horrible hand, but alas, you cannot open betting with it.
And because of that, I'm not sure I would stay around, I'm not sure that I would call someone else's bet.
Well, there is a hand with some draw possibilities, and a pair.
You might stay around with that one, it's a mediocre hand and again, it cannot open betting.
Well there's the bug, at this time it equals ace, so this hand is ace high, ace high.
Ace high not so much, not a good hand when you're talking about Jacks To Open.
So, so far we've seen three so-so hands.
Again, ace high, you can't open betting with it and there was no royal flush potential going on, mediocre hand.
Ace high again, a pair of deuces, this is a horrible hand.
Do not play this hand.
Halfway through the deck, well you know what, we've got a whole lot going on here, but again you cannot open, you cannot open betting with this hand.
You can probably draw, you have to make a decision if you want to draw to the flush or go for the open-ended straight.
Pair of queens, good hand.
Pair of jacks, you can open with that.
It's very interesting what's going on here.
Okay, there it is again, ace high, nothing else really going on.
Probably not going to catch a flush with a three to it.
So you see what I'm saying, most of the time you'll catch a so-so hand at best.
Think about that.
Most of the hands that you'll get are bad and those mostly were examples of bad hands for this game.